其它狗也在附近相似的公园里找到
The other dogs were found in a similar park not far away.
有一只除外  它在离这一英里外的小巷被发现
Except for the one found in an alley about a mile from here.
里德
Hey, Reid.
记得那些时光吧
You remember those days?
不怎么记得
Mm, not really.
你年少时一般去哪逛
Well, where did you hang out as a teenager?
图书馆  化学实验室  图书馆
Library, chemistry lab, library--
不  不  不  我说的是那些
No, no, no, no, no. I'm talking about normal,
普通非天才青少年会去的地方
non-genius teenage type of stuff.
商场  咖啡店
Malls, coffee shops,
公园
parks.
我们来的路上经过了一个商场和两家咖啡店
We passed a mall and two coffee shops on the way here.
还有一个高中
And a high school, too.
那就能解释为什么不明嫌犯这么冲动
That would explain why the unsub's so impulsive.
他可能还是个青少年
He might still be an adolescent.